<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>premier-inn on Disability Watch</title><link>/tags/premier-inn/</link><description>Recent content in premier-inn on Disability Watch</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/premier-inn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blind woman and guide dog kicked out of London Premier Inn</title><link>/p/blind-woman-and-guide-dog-kicked-out-of-london-premier-inn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/blind-woman-and-guide-dog-kicked-out-of-london-premier-inn/</guid><description>&lt;p>Angharad Paget-Jones, a data analyst and disability rights campaigner from Port Talbot writes on Twitter about the experience of being forced to leave the Premier Inn at Enfield, in the middle of the night.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Source:&lt;/strong> &lt;a class="link" href="https://twitter.com/AngieBeatDown/status/1590388040937406473" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Twitter&lt;/a>&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Archive:&lt;/strong> &lt;a class="link" href="https://archive.ph/z17xH" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>archive.ph&lt;/a> &lt;a class="link" href="https://threadreaderapp.com/thread/1590388040937406473.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>threadreader&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>UPDATE&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
On the 11th November 2022, Premier Inn released the following statement on &lt;a class="link" href="https://twitter.com/premierinn/status/1591111307188916225" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Twitter&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>At Premier Inn we take the needs and equal treatment of our guests extremely seriously
and all team members receive disability awareness training to make sure all our guests
get the same warm welcome and enjoy a great stay. So we were shocked and appalled to see
the upsetting Twitter thread alleging that a guest was asked to leave one of our hotels in
Enfield.
An urgent investigation is already underway with the hotel to find out exactly what's happened
and we've reached out to the guest to fully understand the circumstances of what has taken place
and apologise for the upset caused. We have a zero tolerance approach towards discrimination and
work extensively with organisations that support disabled people - this only strengthens our
determination to ensure this kind of incident never happens again.
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>UPDATE 2&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
On the 12th November 2022 MP Feryal Clark received a &lt;a class="link" href="https://twitter.com/FeryalClark/status/1591464707709456384" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>response&lt;/a> from Premier Inn&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director, Alison Brittain regarding the incident pledging to investigate.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>